qmee.com 2017-03-26

# Privacy policy - Qmee.com

This privacy policy (together with our terms and conditions and any other documents referred to within) governs the collection, storage and use of personal information collected by us, Qmee Ltd, in providing our service, including our website at www.qmee.com and our qmee browser application software (which is available for download via the website). It provides you with details about the personal information we collect from you, how we use your personal information and your rights to control personal information we hold about you.

Please read this privacy policy carefully – by accessing or browsing this website, you confirm that you have read, understood and agree to this privacy policy in its entirety. If you do not agree to this privacy policy in its entirety, you must not use our service, including this website and any software available for download on the website.

This privacy policy was last updated on _22 March 2016_. Please check back regularly to keep informed of updates to this privacy policy.

#### Who we are

Qmee Ltd is a company registered in England and Wales (registration number 07455925), whose registered office is at 3 Wesley Gate, Queens Road, Reading, Berkshire, RG1 4AP.

We respect your right to privacy and will only process personal information you provide to us in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998, the Privacy and Electronic Communications (EC Directive) Regulations 2003 and other applicable privacy laws.

If you have any questions about how we collect, store and use personal information, or if you have any other privacy-related questions, please e-mail us at [support@qmee.com.](mailto:support@qmee.com)

#### The personal information we collect about you

In order for you to use our service, we will need to collect the following personal information from you:

  * your e-mail address;
  * your country of residence;
  * your Paypal account details;
  * your search history and details of sponsored links that you click on when using our service; and
  * details of your behaviour on the sites linked to by our service, namely the pages you browse and for how long you browse those pages.

You may voluntarily submit the following additional personal information:

  * your name;
  * your age and sex;
  * your town of residence; and
  * your postal address, phone and fax details.

#### How we may store and use your information

We (or third party data processors acting on our behalf) may collect, store and use your personal information listed above for the following purposes:

  * to make our service, including this website, available to you and to provide you with content which is tailored to your individual tastes;
  * to provide you with sponsored search results which we think may interest you via our software;
  * to make payments to you or to third parties on your instructions via this website;
  * to assess whether you are abusing our service contrary to our terms and conditions;
  * to carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us;
  * to notify you about changes to our service;
  * where you have given us your consent, to contact you (including by SMS and e-mail) with products and services which we think may interest you; and

We will not disclose, sell or rent your personal information to any third party unless you have consented to this. If you do consent but later change your mind, you may contact us and we will cease any such activity.

However, if a third party acquires all (or substantially all) of our business and/or assets, we may disclose your personal information to that third party in connection with the acquisition. We may also disclose your personal information where we are required to do so by applicable law, by a governmental body or by a law enforcement agency.

We may also collect anonymised details about users of our service, including visitors to our website and users of our software, for the purposes of aggregate statistics or reporting purposes. However, no single individual will be identifiable from the anonymised details we collect for these purposes.

We do not disclose information about identifiable individuals to our advertisers or partners, but we may provide them with aggregate information about our users (for example, we may inform them that 500 men aged under 30 have clicked on their sponsored link on any given day). We may also use such aggregate information to help advertisers or partners reach the kind of audience they want to target (for example, women in SW1 or a US ZIP code). We may make use of the personal data we have collected from you to enable us to comply with our advertisers' wishes by displaying their sponsored links to that target audience.

Please note that when you take part in a survey, the survey partner who operates it may ask you for information (including but not limited to your year of birth, postcode or ZIP code, gender and survey responses). You acknowledge that, by submitting the survey, any such information will be shared with the survey partner.

#### International transfers

We may transfer personal information that we collect from you to third party data processors located in countries that are outside of the European Economic Area (including to United States) in connection with the above purposes. Please be aware that countries which are outside the European Economic Area may not offer the same level of data protection as the United Kingdom, although our collection, storage and use of your personal data will continue to be governed by this privacy policy.

#### Cookies

A cookie is a small file of letters and numbers that we store on your browser or the hard drive of your computer. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer's hard drive. Our website uses cookies to distinguish you from other users of our website. This helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse our website and also allows us to improve our site. We use "analytical" cookies to recognise and count the number of visitors and to see how visitors move around the site when they are using it. This helps us to improve the way our website works, for example, by ensuring that users are finding what they are looking for easily. If you register with us or complete our online forms, we will use cookies to remember your details during your current visit, and any future visits provided the cookie was not deleted in the interim. If you click on sponsored results when using our service you may be redirected to the partner/advertiser's site via affiliate cookies. You can disable and/or delete all types of cookies by using your browser settings. Cookies are generally easy to disable and/or delete but how you do so varies from browser to browser. The "help" function within your browser should tell you how to do it. However, if you use your browser settings to block all cookies (including essential cookies) you may not be able to make use of all or part of our website or service. For further information about cookies please visit [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).

#### Security

Whilst we take appropriate technical and organisational measures to safeguard the personal information that you provide to us, no transmission over the Internet can ever be guaranteed secure. Consequently, please note that we cannot guarantee the security of any personal information that you transfer over the Internet to us.

#### Your rights

You have the following rights:

  * the right to ask us to provide you with copies of personal information that we hold about you at any time, subject to a fee specified by law (currently £10);
  * the right to ask us to close your user account and remove all of the personal data that we hold about you, other than data that we are required to hold under statute;
  * the right to ask us to update and correct any out-of-date or incorrect personal information that we hold about you free of charge; and
  * the right to opt out of any marketing communications that we (or any third party to whom we have disclosed your personal information with your consent) may send you.

If you wish to exercise any of the above rights, please write to us by e-mail at the address specified above.

#### Third party sites

This website contains links to other websites operated by third parties. Please note that this privacy policy applies only to the personal information that we collect and we cannot be responsible for personal information that third parties may collect, store and use through their websites. Once you click on a link to a third party's website, including sponsored links provided in the Qmee window, that third party's collection, storage and use of your personal information is out of our control. You should always read the privacy policy of each website you visit carefully.
